Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
=Vengeful Wife=
=Episode 21=
Don't get closer.
No.
Ye Dong.
What are you up to?
You almost scared me to death.
I just had a hallucination.
I thought I saw Lin Xia.
You've done so many shady things.
It's so late.
What are you doing here?
I wanted to see you.
You've seen me.
You can leave now.
Do you
not miss me at all?
No.
Ye Dong,
you destroyed my family
and want me to miss you?
Yes.
I did use some tricks.
But I helped you
see Cheng Nuo's true color.
So we
can forgive each other.
No.
Let go of me.
Ye Dong,
let go of me.
No.
Let go of me.
Ye Dong.
You've changed.
In the past,
even if you refused,
when I forced you,
you'd fight till the end.
But now,
you seem so indifferent.
People
do change.
You can't live in the past forever.
You aren't in a good state today.
Why not
go out first?
Lately,
I've been a bit tired.
Take a good rest.
Tomorrow,
I'll pick you up.
Mom,
don't eavesdrop.
If you're so curious,
go in and listen.
Follow me.
(This scent)
(can tap into people's
subconscious fears.)
(Be careful.)
(I don't have any emotions,)
(including fear.)
You're a famous entrepreneur now.
Why did you grovel before a woman?
There's no woman you can't get now.
Bai Cha is different.
Her heart
has never truly belonged to me.
I must conquer her.
That's more thrilling than anything.
Look at how pathetic you are.
As your mother,
I have plenty of ways to deal with her.
What ways?
Stop messing around.
Ms. Lin, how does it feel
to return to Jiuyao?
Mr. Luo,
what brings you here?
Just now,
you called me?
It's Bai Cha.
I only saw your back
and made a mistake.
Then,
Ms. Lin you mentioned was...
Jiuyao's former chairman
and CEO,
Lin Xia.
You look different,
but everything else
feels the same.
From your tone,
you seem to be quite familiar
with Lin Xia.
Right.
I even personally
examined her body.
Mr. Luo,
what do you mean?
They said
Lin Xia is at large.
What are you...
Oh! This is bad!
Why
did I blurt that out?
Remember,
keep this secret.
By the way,
I heard today
you'll take over as CEO.
Lin Xia used
to be Jiuyao's CEO.
You two do
have a special bond.
Mr. Luo,
I have urgent business.
I'll get going.
Okay.
(Mr. Luo suspects my identity.)
(CEO Appointment Letter)
Ms. Bai,
we heard you were a hostess in clubs.
How
did you become
a renowned group's CEO step by step?
Hello,
this reporter.
First,
let me correct one thing.
I worked as nightclub DJ,
not hostess.
Moreover,
I studied business management theories
and got the certificates
through hard work.
Everyone,
today
I have another announcement to make.
Ye Dong, Jiuyao Group's
chairman,
has decided
to transfer ten percent of his shares
to me
as encouragement.
Here,
I want to express gratitude
to Ye Dong.
Mr. Ye,
are you giving Ms. Bai so many shares
because you fancy her?
My heart has always belonged
to my ex-wife Lin Xia alone,
though she...
The shares transfer to Ms. Bai
is a recognition of her business acumen.
I hope Ms. Bai will
contribute to our group's success
and achieve win-win cooperation.
Alright,
today's press conference
concludes here.
Thank you all.
Transfer ten percent...
Ten percent of his shares!
That's astronomical wealth.
He's so generous.
Don't judge him by normal standards.
Qiao,
run a DNA comparison
between this hair
and Bai Cha's
blood sample
from the crime scene.
I need results as soon as possible.
Whose hair is this?
Bai Cha's.
Master,
what's this about?
We have her blood sample.
Her hair
will be redundant.
No more questions.
Also,
compare this hair's DNA
with that
of Lin Xia's body.
Bai Cha and Lin Xia?
That's impossible!
What are you trying to prove?
I can't follow your logic.
It hurts.
It hurts?
You've lost your mind.
Daring to spout
nonsense
before the media.
Ten percent of my shares?
Why don't you just rob?
The shares are under your name.
If you refuse to transfer, then don't.
Or
are you going to go
back on your word?
Do you realize you're
slandering and ruining me?
I wonder how you
managed to sweet talk Lin Xia
into transferring all her shares to you.
She gave you everything
as she loved you so much.
But I'm
asking for ten percent from you,
less than one-fifth of what you get.
You are so furious now.
Ye Dong.
Did you obtain your position
by deceiving Lin Xia?
♪Like a forgotten flower♪
♪Silently scattered across the horizon♪
♪Bathed in silent starlight♪
♪One day it will bloom♪
♪Let time heal the wounds♪
♪Clench the trembling hands♪
♪Embrace the faith of rebirth♪
♪The ending won't come too late♪
♪Under the mask♪
♪Observing all truths and lies♪
♪Who can see my strength♪
♪Tears soak my face♪
♪Under the mask♪
♪Seeking light in the darkness♪
♪What couldn't be let go♪
♪Eventually turns to dust in the wind♪
♪Under the mask♪
♪Observing all truths and lies♪
♪Who can see my strength♪
♪Tears soak my face♪
♪Under the mask♪
♪Seeking light in the darkness♪
♪What couldn't be let go♪
♪Eventually turns to dust in the wind♪